Elmo Roper Papers
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Jobs, 1953-1961
  - Job 302, Citizenship Survey, 1957-1961
    - Correspondence--England, 1958 April - 1959 March, 1960 (Box 43:2611)
    - Correspondence--England, 1959 April - May (Box 43:2612)
    - Correspondence--England, 1959 June - August (Box 43:2613)
    - Correspondence--England, 1959 September - December (Box 43:2614)
    - Correspondence--Field, 1958, 1960 (Box 43:2615)
    - Correspondence--Field, 1959 January - May (Box 43:2616)
    - Correspondence--Field, 1959 June - December (Box 43:2617)
    - Correspondence--Germany, 1958 (Box 43:2618)
    - Correspondence--Germany, 1959 March - April (Box 43:2619)
    - Correspondence--Germany, 1959 May - July (Box 43:2620)
    - Correspondence--Germany, 1959 August - December (Box 43:2621)
    - Correspondence--Germany, 1960-1961 (Box 43:2622)
    - Correspondence--Holland, 1959 August - November (Box 43:2623)
    - Correspondence--Holland, 1959 November - 1960 January (Box 43:2624)
    - Correspondence--Italy, 1958 (Box 43:2625)
    - Correspondence--Italy, 1959 February - April (Box 43:2626)
    - Correspondence--Italy, 1959 May (Box 43:2627)
    - Correspondence--Italy, 1959 June - August (Box 43:2628)
    - Correspondence--Italy, 1959 September - 1960 September (Box 43:2629)
    - Correspondence--Mexico, 1959 February - April (Box 43:2630)
    - Correspondence--Mexico, 1959 May (Box 43:2631)
    - Correspondence--Mexico, 1959 September - November (Box 43:2632)
    - Correspondence--Mexico, 1959 June - August (Box 43:2633)
    - Correspondence--Mexico, 1959 December - 1960 January (Box 43:2634)
    - Correspondence--Sweden/France (Box 43:2635)
    - Data (Box 41)
    - Data--Anderson, Harriet Interview (Box 43:2636-2637)
    - Data--Hampton Interview (Box 43:2638-2640)
    - Documentation--Financials/Background material (Box 43:2641)
    - Documentation--Interoffice/Background notes (Box 43:2642)
    - Documentation--Political life history pretest (English) (Box 43:2643)
    - Documentation--Political life history pretest (German) (Box 43:2644)
    - Documentation--Proposal (Box 43:2645)
    - Questionnaire (draft) (Box 43:2646-2647)
    - Questionnaires (Box 43:2648)
    - Documentation--Technical notes (Italy/Mexico) (Box 43:2649)
  - Job 303, Birmingham Amoco Study, 1957-1958
    - Correspondence, 1957 December - 1958 June (Box 43:2650)
    - Correspondence, 1958 July (Box 43:2651)
    - Correspondence, 1958 July - September (Box 43:2652)
    - Data (Box 41)
    - Data--Interview (Box 43:2653-2657)
    - Data--Sample listings (Box 43:2658-2659)
    - Data--Sample tract sheets (Box 44:2660-2665)
    - Data--Tabulations (preliminary) (Box 44:2666)
    - Data--Tabulations (Box 44:2667-2668)
    - Documentation--Background materials (Box 44:2669)
    - Documentation--Survey design (Box 44:2670)
  - Job 304, undated
    - Data (Box 41)
- Series VI: Scrapbooks, Calendars and Ephemera, undated, 1921-1970
  - Subseries A: Scrapbooks, 1941-1970
    - 1935-1941 (Box 45)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 46)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 47)
    - 1944-1949 (Box 52)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 48)
    - 1948 (Box 49)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 50)
    - 1951-1952 July (Box 51)
    - 1952-1954 (Box 53)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 54)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 55)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 56)
    - 1962 (Box 57)
    - 1963-1965 (Box 58)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 59)
    - 1967-1969 (Box 60)
    - 1968-1970 (Box 61)
  - Subseries B: Calendars, 1942-1970
    - Calendars (29 volumes), 1942-1970 (Box 62)
  - Subseries C: Office Handbooks, 1941-1969
    - Foreign Policy, "Atlantic Union", World Peace, 1948-1969 (Box 63)
    - Manual, undated (Box 63)
    - Politics, Political Polling and Analysis, 1941-1968 (Box 63)
  - Subseries D: Ephmera, undated, 1921-1965
    - Pins, buttons, passports, wallets, snapshots, etc., undated (Box 64)
    - Certificates and citations, 1921-1965 (Box OS)